我到底哪里有问题? 我看起来不够风趣吗?
Okay. What is it about me? Do I not look fun enough?
我到底哪里让人讨厌?
Is there something repellent about me?
派对好玩么?
How was the party?
糟透了 有个女人把我当空气一样穿过去
It couldn't have been worse. A woman literally passed through me.
到底怎么了 我真的无可救药的不吸引人吗?
So, what is it? Am I hideously unattractive?
不 才怪 你非常有魅力
No, you are not. You are very attractive.
我也有过同样的经历
You know I go through the exact same thing.
每次我变胖一点点 我就会开始质疑一切
Every time I put on a little weight, I start questioning everything.
哇哦
Whoa, whoa.
我变胖了?
I've put on a little weight?
你想不想?      是的
Did you want to...?        Yeah, uh...
不是变胖 是变得更稳重
No, not weight. You know, more like insulation.
钱德 我现在失业了 我迫切需要做点什么事儿
Chandler, I'm unemployed, indire need of a project.
你想锻炼吗? 我可以打造全新的你
Wanna work out? I can remake you.
我很想 但那样我就没时间懒散了
Uh, you know I would, but that might get in the way of my lying around time.
拜托      好啦 让她帮你!
Please?        Come on. Let her do it!
好吧 但穿上紧身衣之后
Okay, all right. But if we put on spandex...
如果我的胸部比你大 我就回家了
and my boobs are bigger than yours, I'm going home.
你的胸部没问题 我真不该说这些 过来 过来
Your boobs are fine. Look, I never should have said anything. Come here. Come here!
两只手合抱不起来!
Ooh. Can't make hands meet!
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧
《老友记》蓝光版 第02季 第07集
罗斯发现了 The One Where Ross Finds Out
调校制作：海盗美剧 寒 枫
字幕编辑：海盗美剧 悠悠慕雪
来吧! 开始吧
Okay! Let's do it.
怎么了?
What?
没事 只是以前从没看过你穿紧身裤
Nothing. Just never seen you in little stretchy pants before.
我去换衣服
And we're changing.
加油 再来五个      不!
Come on, give me five more!        No!
再来五个!      不要!
Five more!        Ugh. Aah!
再来五个我就给你看咪咪
Five more and I'll flash you.
一
One
二
two
二点五
two and a half.
给我看一边吧
Okay. Just show me one of them.
她疯了 那女人疯了
She's insane! The woman is insane.
上班前 下班后 甚至上班时
It's before work, it's after work, and it's during work.
她要我在上班时在办公桌前做收臀运动
She's got me doing butt clenches at my desk.
现在他们都不给我送邮件了
And now they won't bring me my mail anymore.
菲比 和史考特约会怎么样?
Hey, Pheebs. How'd it go with Scott last night?
额 不错 带他去了一家很浪漫的餐厅
Oh urn, it was nice. Took him to a romantic restaurant
点了香槟 很好
ordered champagne. Nice.
还是没动静?      没 完全没动静
The guy still won't put out?        Nope. Zilch. Nothing. Uhuh.
抱歉 菲比
Sorry, Pheebs.
我不介意慢慢来 我很喜欢他
Well, look, I don't mind taking it slow. I like him a lot.
他很风趣 又很体贴
He's really interesting, and he's really sweet.
他为什么那么矜持呢!?
Why won't he give it up?
也许他是"另外一边的"
Maybe he, uh, drives his car on the other side of the road.
如果你懂我的意思
If you know what I mean.
不懂 什么意思? 他又不是英国人
No. What do you mean? He's not British.
或许他是同性恋
Maybe he's gay.
我觉得不是那个问题
Urn, no, I don't think that's the problem.
我们前几天去跳舞
cause we went, urn, dancing the other night
他紧紧抱住我的样子 他凝视我的眼睛的样子
and just the way he held me so close and the way he was looking into my eyes
我觉得他肯定对我有意思
I just definitely felt something.
但是眼神能看出什么呢?
Yeah, but how much can you tell from a look?
不 我从屁股感觉到的 我知道
No, I felt it on my hip. I could tell.
哟 宾 二十分钟后去打壁球
Yo, Bing! Racquet ball in 20 minutes.
乔伊 行行好 把我的手抬起来给她一拳
Joey, be a pal. Lift up my hand and smack her with it.
喔 瑞秋! 别看!      什么?
Ooh. Oh, Rachel! Don't look.        What?
拜托 我才不在乎 我今晚有约会
Come on, guys. I don't care. I have a date tonight.
哇 哇 哇 你有约会?      是的 摩妮卡介绍的
Whoa, whoa, whoa. You have a date?        Yeah. Monica's setting me up.
额 那罗斯和...
Heh, now, what about, uh, Ross and...
什么 我很爱乱吃醋的事?
What? My whole insane jealousy thing?
好吧 尽管这还挺有趣
Well, you know, as much fun as that was
我决定不再疯下去了
I've decided to opt for sanity.
你已经不介意了?
So you're okay about all this?
哦 当然 拜托! 我已经往前看了
Oh, yeah, come on! I'm moving on.
他想怎么将她压在那扇窗户上就怎么样吧
He can press her up against that window as much as he wants.
他都可以直接将她从窗户扔进来 我各种不介意
For all I care, he can throw her through the damn thing.
嗨 各位      嘿
Hi, guys.        Hey.
摩妮卡 我明早过来拿毛毛以前的猫玩具
Monica, I figured I'd come by tomorrow and pick up Fluffy's old cat toys, okay?
除非你说出他的全名
Only if you say his full name.
我明天是否能过来拿毛毛喵喵的猫玩具?
Can I come over tomorrow and pick up Fluffy Meowington's cat toys?
好的      你要养猫?
All right.        You're getting a cat?
事实上 是我们要养
Actually, we're getting a cat.
一起?
Together?
你们俩? 一起?      是的
Both of you? Together?        Yup.
它一半时间和我住 一半时间和罗斯住
It'll live with Ross half the time and me half the time.
哦
Oh, well
真幸福 你们俩将可以享受
Isn't that just lovely? Ha. That's something the two of you will be able to enjoy
这种幸福的感觉很长很长很长一段时间呢
for a really, really, really long time.
希望如此
Hopefully. Oh, wow.
哎呀 看 我得走了! 我要去约会呢!
Whoa! Look at that. I gotta go! I got a date!
和男人约会哈
With a man. Ahem, okay.
祝你们大家晚安
You guys have a really, uh, good night
祝你们俩找到一只很棒的猫
and you two have a, uh, really good cat. Heh.
顺手牵羊是不对的
Okay. We're not supposed to take these when we leave.
摩妮卡大概告诉过你 这是我离婚之后第一次约会
I don't know if Monica told you, but this the first date I've gone on since my divorce.
如果我看起来有点紧张
So if I seem a little nervous
事实上我是的
I am.
猫能活多久?
How long do cats live?
什么?      猫 通常能活几年?
I'm sorry.        Cats. How long do they live?
如果不是把它们丢到公共车底下的话?
Figuring you don't throw them under a bus or something?
额 大概十五 六年吧      好吧 那真棒
Urn, maybe 15, 16 years.        Well, that's just great.
干杯!
Urn. Cheers.
是啊 干杯!
Right. Clink. Heh.
摩妮卡把我吹得比本人可爱 是吧?
Monica told you I was cuter than this. Didn't she?
噢 不 麦可 和你没关系 只是...
Oh, no. Michael, it's not you. Sorry. It's just..
是这样的 可能听起来没那么糟糕
It's this thing. It's probably not as bad as it sounds...
但我有个朋友和他的女朋友 正打算养一只猫
but this friend of mine is getting a cat with his girlfriend.
哦 那听起来确实...
Oh, that does sound...
他才刚开始和她交往
I mean he just started going out with her.
额 他是你前男友吗?
Ahem. Is this guy, uh, an old boyfriend?
他想的美!
Yeah, he wishes.
真抱歉 我真失礼
Oh, I'm sorry. Look at me.
麦可 咱们来聊聊你吧
Okay, Michael, let's talk about you.
好的      好的
All right.        Okay. Okay?
那么
So
你曾经和女友一起养过宠物吗?
Did you ever get a pet with a girlfriend?
我知道为什么了      什么?
So I figured it out.        What?
关于史考特不肯和我上床的原因
Why Scott doesn't want to sleep with me.
我不够性感
I'm not sexy enough.
菲比 太扯了
Heh, Phoebe, that's crazy.
我刚认识你时 你知道我怎么对钱德说的吗?
When I first met you, you know what I said to Chandler?
我说 "前凸后翘 有看头"
I said, "Excellent butt, great rack."
真的吗? 你真好
Really? That's so sweet.
我是说我绝对被冒犯了 但那真体贴
I mean, I'm officially offended. But that's so sweet.
如果你真想知道实情 你得亲自问他
Look, if you wanna know what the deal is, you're just gonna have to ask him.
你说得对 没错
You're right. You're right.
你真棒
Ugh, you are so yum!
只不过是一只猫 你知道么? 一只猫
I mean it's a cat, you know? It's a cat.
他们为什么不养虫子? 养果蝇嘛
Why can't they get one of those bugs? You know, one of those fruit flies.
那种只活一天 叫什么来着的? 叫什么来着的?
Those things that live for a day. Something. What are they called? What are they called?
果蝇?      没错!
Fruit flies?        Yes!
谢谢你
Thank you.
你们要吃甜点吗?      不要! 不要甜点
Would you like any dessert?        No! No dessert.
请买单吧
Just the check. Please.
哦 不 你和我在一起不开心吧?
Oh, no. You're not having fun, are you?
不 不 我开心
No, no. I am.
因为刚刚一个半小时以来
But only because for last hour and a half
我脑袋里一直在回忆电影"餐馆"的情节
I've been playing the movie Diner in my head.
哦 我真是的
Oh. Look at me.
看看我
Look at me.
我正在和一个很棒的男人约会
Oh, I'm on a date with a really great guy.
我心里却只想着罗斯和他的猫
All I can think about is Ross and his cat.
还有他的茱莉
and his Julie.
我只想忘了他 为什么我做不到呢?
I just want to get over him. God why can't I do that?
哦
Oh.
听着 我离过婚 相信我 你会没事的
Look, I've been through a divorce. Trust me, you're gonna be fine.
你现在看不出来是因为你和他还没了结
You can't see it now because you haven't had closure.
哈! 了结!
Aah! Closure!
就是那个! 那正是我需要的!
That's what it is. That's what I need.
老天 你真聪明!
God, you're brilliant!
为什么我没想到呢? 要怎么了结呢?
Why didn't I think of that? How do I get that?
并没有一定的办法 只是
Well, there's no one way really, it's just
无论什么办法 只要能让你对他说
you know, whatever it takes so that you can finally say to him
"我不在乎你了"
"I'm over you."
不在乎你了
Over you.
那才是关键
That's what it is.
了结
Closure.
嗨 对不起
Hello? Excuse me?
抱歉 哇哦
Excuse me. Hel...Whoo!
等会      你好 对不起
Hang on.        Hello? Excuse me?
怎么了?      嗨 抱歉
What?        Hi. I'm sorry.
我需要借你的电话 只要一分钟
I need to borrow your phone for just one minute.
我正在讲电话      我看得出来
I'm talking.        I can see that.
就打一个电话 很快 我甚至可以付你钱
It's one phone call, I'll be very quick. I'll even pay for it myself.
你对你的电话有点诡异额
Okay, you're being a little weird about your phone.
好吧
All right. Fine.
我再打给你
I'll call you back.
谢谢
Thank you.
好
Okay.
是答录机
Machine.
在等哔声      很好
Just waiting for the beep.        Good.
罗斯! 嗨 是我 瑞秋
Ross! Hi, it's Rachel.
我打电话来是要告诉你 额
I'm just calling to say that, urn...
一切都很好 我很为你高兴
everything's fine. And I'm really happy for you
还有你的猫
and your cat.
哦对了 你应该给你的猫取名麦可
Who, by the way, I think you should name Michael.
你看 我连名字都想好了
And you know, you see there, I'm thinking of names.
所以明显我已经不在乎你了
So obviously I am over you.
我不在乎你了
I am over you.
那就是 我朋友说的所谓的"了结"
And that, my friend, is what they call "closure".
不 不 不
No, no, no, no, no, no. No.
不 不 不!
No, no, no
摩妮卡 今天是星期天 我星期天不跑步
Monica, it's Sunday morning. I'm not running on a Sunday.
为什么?      因为是星期天!
Why not?        Because it's Sunday!
是上帝的日子
It's God's day.
嘿 只要你说停 我们就停
Ha, hey. If you say stop, and we stop.
好
Ha, ha, okay.
停!
Stop.
不 拜托 我们不能停! 还有三磅要减!
No, come on! We can't stop! Come on. We got three more pounds to go!
我是精力充沛的火车 你在火车上
I am the energy train and you are on board!
嘿 瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
约会如何?
Oh. And how was the date?
额 我记得有家餐厅
Urn, I think there was a restaurant.
我知道有酒
I know there was wine.
哇哦 好吧
Wow. Well, uh...
呃 事实上茱莉正在楼下叫出租车
Uh, actually, Julie's downstairs, getting a cab.
我上来拿猫玩具 摩妮卡有没有说?
I just need the cat toys. Did Monica say?
怎么了? 你为什么那样看我?
What? Why, why are you looking at me like that? Heh.
对不起 我不知道 我...
Ahem, I'm sorry. I don't know, I...
我昨晚好像梦到了你
I feel like I had a dream about you last night
但我不记得了
but I don't remember.
好吧
Okay.
在那儿
There they are.
我们昨晚有通电话吗? 你打给我没?
Did we speak on the phone? Did you call me?
没有 我昨晚住在茱莉家
No. I stayed at Julie's last night.
我根本还没回家呢 我可以查一下留言吗?
Oh, actually I haven't even been home yet. Do you mind if I check my messages?
哦 好 你查吧
Oh, yeah, go ahead.
瑞秋 我有一通你的留言!
Rach, I got a message from you!
谁是麦可?      哦 天呐!
Who's Michael?        Oh, my God.
天呐 罗斯 挂断电话
God, Ross, no! Hang up the phone.
电话给我 电话给我 电话给我
Give me the phone! Give me the phone! Give me the phone!
给我...
Give me the...
你已经不在乎我了?
You're over me?
哦 老天!
Oh. God.
什么? 你? 额...      哦天
Wha? You're,uh...        Oh, God.
你不在乎我了      天呐 天呐 天呐
You're over me        Oh, God, oh, God, oh, God.
天啊
Oh, my God. Oh...
什么时候? 你什么时候
When? When were you
在乎我?
under me?
瑞秋
Rach.
瑞秋 你?
Rachel, do you?
你曾经有过?
I mean were you, uh?
什么?      好吧 好吧
What?        Ugh. Okay. Okay, okay.
嗯 基本上
Well, basically
最近 我是有点 额
lately, I've, uh...
我对你似乎有感觉
Ahem, I've sort of had feelings for you.
你对我有感觉?
You've had feelings for me?
是的 那又怎样? 是你先对我有感觉的!
Yeah, what? so? You had feelings for me first.
你知道我? 你知道我曾经?
You know about my? I mean, you know I had?
你知道?
You know?
钱德告诉我了
Chandler told me.
钱德 他什么时候说的? 什么时候? 什么时候?
Chandler. When did he? When did he? When did he?
你去中国的时候      中国
When you were in China.        China.
遇见茱莉的时候      茱莉
Meeting Julie.        Julie.
茱莉 那...哦 上帝!
Julie. That's...Oh, God.
茱莉? 茱莉 是的
Julie? Julie, right.
好吧 我需要躺下来
Okay, I need to lie down.
不 我要站着 我得站着...
No, you know, I'm gonna stand. I'm gonna stand...
我还要走动一下 我要走动并且站着
and I'm gonna walk. I'm walking and I am standing.
所以你...
Okay, so you, uh...?
现在 什么? 现在? 现在
And now, what? Now? Now.
现在你不在乎我了么?
Now you're over me?
那你还在乎我么?
Are you over me?
那是茱莉 茱莉 茱莉
That's, that's Julie. That's Julie. Julie.
嗨 茱莉      亲爱的 出租车在等呢
Hi Julie.        Hi honey, I'v egot a cab waiting.
我马上下来!
I'll be right down!
等等 你要走了?
Wait, so you're going?
我得走了 我现在没办法处理这事儿
Well, okay, I, uh, I have to. I can't deal with this right now.
我是说 出租车在等我
I mean, I've, uh Heh. You know I've got a cab.
我有个女朋友 我要养一只猫
I've got a girlfriend. I'm gonna go get a cat.
好的
Okay. Okay.
猫!
Cat!
嘿 乔伊      嘿 菲比
Hey, Joey.        Hey, Pheebs.
你怎么在看犹太牧师弹电吉他?
How come you're watching a rabbi play electric guitar?
我找不到摇控器
I can't find the remote.
谢谢
Ugh, thank you. Heh.
史考特叫我去他家吃午餐 我去了
So, Scott asked me to come over for lunch today and I did.
然后呢?      我们做了!
And?        And we did.
好啊 菲比! 太棒了!      我好棒啊!哈哈
All right, Pheebs! Way to go!        Yay, me. Ha, ha.
那么是怎么发生的?
So how did it happen?
我听了你的建议 问他到底是怎么回事
I finally took your advice and asked him what was going on.
他怎么说?      他说
What did he say?        He said that
他知道女人对性特别感情用事
he understands how sex can be like, a very emotional thing for a woman.
他害怕我会胡思乱想 你知道的
And he was just afraid that I was going to get all, you know
"他第二天会打电话么?"
"Is he gonna call me the next day?"
和"这段感情有没有未来?"之类的
and "Where is this going?" and blaaaaa
所以他说他想等到他准备好定下来再说
So he said he wanted to hold off until he was prepared to be serious.
哇哦      是的
Wow.        Yeah.
所以我说"好的 放轻松"
So I said, "Okay. Relax, please." You know?
我是说 性可以只是两个人一时的感觉
I mean, sex can be just about two people right there in the moment.
如果他想再和我约会 他就打电话
If he wants to see me again, he can call.
如果不想也没关系
And if not, that's fine too.
然后在我们谈了很久之后
So after a lot of talking, heh...
我说服他了 哈
I convinced him. Heh!
让我把这件事搞清楚 他让你去求他和你上床
Let me get this straight. He got you to beg to sleep with him.
他让你自己说他再也不用打电话给你
He got you to say he never has to call you again.
他还让你认为这是个好主意?
And he got you thinking this is a great idea?
嗯哼
Uhhuh.
这人是我的偶像!
This man is my god.
晚安
Good night
嗨      我没领养猫
Hi.        I didn't get a cat.
哦 真有趣
Oh, that's, urn, interesting.
不 不 一点也不有趣 非常非常没趣
No. No, it's not interesting. Okay? It's very, very not interesting.
事实上百分之百是有趣的反面
It's actually a hundred percent completly the opposite of interesting.
我懂了 罗斯
I got it, Ross.
你无权告诉我你对我有过感觉
You had no right to tell me you ever had feelings for me.
什么?      在我发现之前我和茱莉过得好好的!
What?        I was doing great with Julie before I found out about you.
在我发现你之前我也过的很好啊!
I was doing great before I found out about you!
你以为我看到你和茱莉在一起很好过么?
You think it's easy for me to see you with Julie?
你在我遇见她之前就应该告诉我!
And then you should've said something before I met her.
我不知道啊! 那你怎么从来不跟我说呢?
I didn't know then. And how come you never said anything to me?
因为总是没机会
There was never a good time.
你有一整年的时间 我们每晚都在一起混!
Right. You only had a year. And we only hung out every night!
不 不是
Not not not...
每个晚上
every night.
我不是没有尝试 有太多事情挡在中间
It's not like I didn't try. But you know, all things got in the way.
你知道 像意大利人
You know, like Italian guys
还有前任未婚夫...
or exfiance, or or or...
还有那些意大利男人
Italian guys.
只有一个意大利男人 你的重点是?
Hey. There was one Italian guy, okay? And do you even have a point?
重点是 我现在不需要这个
The point is, I, I don't need this right now!
好吧? 已经太迟了
Okay? It's, it's too late.
我在和别人交往 我很快乐 我这艘船已经出港了
I'm with somebody else. I'm happy. This ship has sailed!
那你是说不管你对我有什么感觉
Okay, what do you say is you're gonna put away feelings
你打算就放在一边?
or whatever it was you felt for me?
我从初三就开始这么做了 我很擅长这个!
I've done it since ninth grade. I've gotten good at it.
好啊 你就继续这么做吧! 罗斯
All right, fine. You go ahead and do that all right, Ross.
我不需要你的蠢船!
I don't need your stupid ship!
很好      很好
Good.        Good!
还有你知道么 现在我已经了结了!
And you know what? Now I got closure!
试试最下面那个
Try the bottom one.
摩妮卡 现在是早上六点半
Monica, it's 6:30 in the morning.
我们不锻炼了 结束了
We're not working out. It's over.
不 只剩一磅了啊 拜托!
No way! With one pound to go? Come on!
我们运动 我们移动 我们在其中 我们在舞动
We're working, we're moving. We're in the zone, we're grooving
最后一磅我无所谓
Okay, I don't, I don't mind the last pound.
事实上我还有点喜欢这最后一磅
Okay, in fact I kind of like the last pound.
所以别让我做出我会后悔的事
So don't make me do anything that I'll regret.
你打算怎样啊 肥仔? 哈哈
Ha, oh, what you gonna do, fat boy, huh? Ha, ha.
怎样?
What? Heh.
没事 除了告诉你 你有这么多精力真棒
Nothing. Except tell you, uh, I think it's wonderful how much energy you have.
谢谢
Well. Thanks.
尤其是现在你找工作找的焦头烂额
Especially considering how tough it's been for you to find work.
你知道
Well, you know. Heh.
是啊 我是说...
You know, I mean...
你不能告诉你爸妈你被开除了 因为他们会很失望
you can't tell your parents you were fired, because they'd be disappointed.
再说你现在又没男朋友让你有个肩膀可以哭
It's not as if you have a boyfriends shoulder to cry on.
是没错 不过我...      我是说...
Well, no. But I...        I mean...
如果换成是我 我一定每天起床都很困难
if it were me, I think I'd have difficulty getting out of bed at all.
你知道我试着保持乐观
You know, I try to stay positive.
所以
So you.
你还想去跑步吗?
You feel like going for a run?
好吧
All right.
你不用勉强 如果你想 你可以在这里睡个觉
Because you don't have to. If you wnat, you could just take a nap right here.
好吧
Okay.
就睡一会      好的
Just for a little while.        Okay.
【海盗美剧 友情制作】
-== http://www.hdmeiju.com ==-
新浪微博：@海盗美剧